Tyler Klink

12461 Anchorage Way, Fishers, IN 46037 tklink53@gmail.com

C# 317.341.3401

Career Summary

Significant experience working with a wide population of individuals from youths, to college students and adults. Demonstrated ability to listen and create trusted connections with individuals in a variety of people facing roles. Received a degree in Communications and Business Ethics.

Sabbatical and Temporary Employment Legends Global Merchandising

November2018-Present

Travel to high profile events all across the United States. Responsible for all logistics involved with each event including, staffing, money management, travel and hotel, event schedule as well as any licensing requirements. Manage temporary staff to assure maximization of sales at each specific retail location. Accountable for all inventory at each available sales location. Oversee the capturing of all sales records and balancing all funds at the end of each event.

Northwestern Mutual-Fishers, Indiana

May 2017-August 2017

Drove new business by qualifying leads, building a strong pipeline, and converting prospects into clients. Reviewed client's goals and assembled insurance and financial solutions to fit the needs of the individual or business. Delivered service aligned with the Northwestern Mutual brand.

Breckenridge Outdoor Education Center - Breckenridge, CO January 2017/2018

The mission of Breckenridge Outdoor Education Center is to expand the potential of people with a wide range of disabilities through meaningful, educational, and inspiring outdoor experiences. BOEC offers an Adaptive Ski and Ride School, Wilderness Programs, Professional Team-building Retreats, and a unique Internship Program.

Youth Ski Instructor

Responsible for providing ski instruction to young people with disabilities utilizing a fleet of new adaptive mono- and bi-skis.

Phi Kappa Psi Fraternity - Greencastle, IN

February 2015 - 2018

Waiter

Responsible for food and beverage delivery and cleaning up after meals.

Varsity Football DePauw-Greencastle, IN

2014-2016

Played offensive guard and center. learned time management and how to balance a full academic and a demanding athletic schedule/continued to develop leadership skills through athletics

All Pro Landscaping - Fishers, IN

Summers 2014, 2015, 2016

Lead Landscaper

Responsible for mowing, planting, mulching, and painting for residential and commercial customers. Helped the owner on numerous jobs

Tyler Klink

12461 Anchorage Way, Fishers, IN 46037 tklink53@gmail.com

C# 317.341.3401

Education

Recieved a Bachelor of Science in Communications and Business Ethics DePauw University - Greencastle, IN (Graduated - May 2018) Phi Psi Philanthropy committee- September 2016- April 2018